# Curriculum Vitae

My name is Samuele.

I'm an Italian spatial data scientist passionate about GIS & programming. Currently, I work at <u>Eurac Research</u> on climate-neutral territories.

The best way to get a hold of me is via email: <a href="mailto:samuelezilio95@gmail.com">samuelezilio95@gmail.com</a>.

You can also find me on GitHub: https://github.com/samuzilio.

## Work Experience

06/2024 - Ongoing

#### Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

05/2021 - 05/2024

#### **Junior Researcher**

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

09/2020 - 04/2021

## **Trainee**

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

## Education

2017 - 2020

### **MSc in Urban and Regional Planning**

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + Universidade de Lisboa, Lisbon (Portugal)

2014 - 2017

### **BSc in Urban and Regional Planning**

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + İstanbul Teknik Üniversitesi, Istanbul (Turkey)